let's look at the answer to our when can
we free the reservation stations quiz if
the instruction cannot issue because
there is no available reservation
station for it that means that all of
our reservation stations are busy with
the processor that doesn't have a Rob we
hold on to our reservation stations from
the time when we issue the instruction
until the time the instruction
broadcasts the result so issuing of an
instruction once the reservation
stations are busy we'll have to wait for
the next instruction to broadcast the
result in contrast in a row based
processor with the same number of
reservation stations we grab them at the
same time when we issue the instruction
but we free them as soon as we dispatch
the instruction for execution
so we free the reservation stations
sooner thus the next instruction might
find the reservation station free over
here where over here it was still not
available so this situation is more
likely to happen when we do not have the
Rob then when we do